export const mockData = [
  {
    category: "Finance",
    question: "What is the total revenue for Q1?",
    answer: 150000,
  },
  {
    category: "Finance",
    question: "What is the profit margin for 2023?",
    answer: 25,
  },
  {
    category: "Finance",
    question: "How much did we spend on marketing?",
    answer: 30000,
  },

  {
    category: "Sales",
    question: "What are the top-selling products number?",
    answer: 100,
  },
  {
    category: "Sales",
    question: "How many new customers did we acquire?",
    answer: 2500,
  },
  {
    category: "HR",
    question: "How many employees joined in 2023?",
    answer: 50,
  },
  {
    category: "HR",
    question: "What is the employee retention rate?",
    answer: 88,
  },
  {
    category: "Marketing",
    question: "Which marketing channels performed best?",
    answer: "Google Ads and LinkedIn performed the best.",
  },
  {
    category: "Marketing",
    question: "What is the conversion rate of the recent campaign?",
    answer: 5.2,
  },

  {
    category: "IT",
    question: "How many system outages occurred last month?",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "IT",
    question: "What is the average response time for customer support?",
    answer: "The average response time is 2 minutes.",
  },
];
